=The Forbidden Woman=
= المرأة المحرمة =
=Episode 11=
= الحلقة 11 =
Why?
لماذا؟
Do you look for me?
هل تبحث عني؟
Is seventy million ready yet?
سبعين مليون جاهز حتى الان؟
I'm
انا
pregnant.
حامل.
You're pregnant?
انت حامل؟
Tell Jiang Fengyan then.
أخبر جيانغ فنغيان بعد ذلك.
Why did you tell me?
لماذا أخبرتني؟
You should let go
يجب أن تترك
of both Fengyan and Xiang Group.
لكل من Fengyan و Xiang Group.
I have to say
يجب أن أقول
that this Biluochun tea
أن شاي بيلوتشون هذا
is the only investment Xiang Tianqiang did
هو الاستثمار الوحيد الذي قام به شيانغ تيان تشيانغ
that doesn't lose money
هذا لا يخسر المال
over these years.
على مدى هذه السنوات.
What I can offer Fengyan
ما يمكنني تقديمه Fengyan
is something you're incapable of.
هو شيء أنت غير قادر عليه.
Are you that sure?
هل أنت متأكد؟
At least
على الأقل
I'm his only legitimate wife now.
أنا زوجته الشرعية الوحيدة الآن.
It's not important what I can offer him.
ليس من المهم ما يمكنني تقديمه له.
The thing is, he can't leave the family.
الشيء هو أنه لا يستطيع ترك العائلة.
You've been with him together for a long time,
لقد كنتم معه سويًا لفترة طويلة ،
Jiang Fengyan should value your feelings,
يجب على جيانغ فنغيان أن يقدر مشاعرك ،
am I right?
هل انا على حق؟
To outsiders,
للغرباء ،
you're the mistress
أنت العشيقة
who has to live in secret.
الذي يجب أن يعيش في الخفاء.
He doesn't love you as much as you thought.
إنه لا يحبك بقدر ما كنت تعتقد.
Don't you play us off against each other.
لا تلعبنا ضد بعضنا البعض.
All you need to do is to keep your promise.
كل ما عليك القيام به هو الوفاء بوعدك.
After I received seventy million,
بعد أن تلقيت سبعين مليونًا ،
I'll leave Jiang Fengyan immediately.
سأترك جيانغ فنغيان على الفور.
By the way, aren't you afraid that someone finds out
بالمناسبة ، ألا تخشى أن يكتشف أحدهم
you sold the shares of Xiang Group at a low price?
قمت ببيع أسهم Xiang Group بسعر منخفض؟
This doesn't concern you though.
هذا لا يعنيك رغم ذلك.
I'll wire the money as soon as possible.
سوف أرسل المال في أقرب وقت ممكن.
Bye-bye.
مع السلامة.
My dear sister.
أختي العزيزة.
I wish
أتمنى
your dreams come true.
احلامك تصبح حقيقة.
Mengmeng.
مينجمينج.
Calm down.
اهدأ.
Please give me some time.
من فضلك أعطني بعض الوقت.
Fengyan.
فنغيان.
I'm really afraid.
أنا خائف حقًا.
This baby doesn't come at the right time.
هذا الطفل لا يأتي في الوقت المناسب.
I'm to blame.
انا الملام.
If it wasn't for me,
إذا لم يكن الأمر كذلك بالنسبة لي ،
it won't turn out this bad.
لن يتحول إلى هذا السوء.
Silly.
سخيف.
Don't overthink.
لا تفرط في التفكير.
Give me some time.
إمنحني بضع الوقت.
I'll take care of everything well.
سأعتني بكل شيء بشكل جيد.
But, I don't want to leave all the pressure
لكني لا أريد أن أترك كل الضغوط
on you alone.
عليك وحدك.
You know what,
أتعلم،
as long as I leave,
ما دمت أغادر ،
everyone will return to the place they used to be
سيعود الجميع إلى المكان الذي اعتادوا أن يكون فيه
and live a happy life.
وعيش حياة سعيدة.
Mengmeng.
مينجمينج.
I made this decision to be with you.
لقد اتخذت هذا القرار لأكون معك.
Don't go.
لا تذهب.
Will you?
سوف تفعل؟
Fengyan.
فنغيان.
Do you really want to keep this baby?
هل تريد حقًا الاحتفاظ بهذا الطفل؟
Of course.
بالتاكيد.
It's our child.
إنه طفلنا.
But
لكن
the baby and I will disgrace both Jiang's and Xiang's families
الطفل وأنا سنخزي عائلات جيانغ وشيانغ
if we stay in this city.
إذا بقينا في هذه المدينة.
A child who's born out of wedlock
الطفل المولود خارج إطار الزواج
would be a laughingstock.
سيكون أضحوكة.
Mengmeng.
مينجمينج.
I'll protect you and the baby well.
سأحميك أنت والطفل جيدًا.
I promise.
أعدك.
After accomplishing the bet-on agreement,
بعد إتمام اتفاقية الرهان ،
I'll fetch both you and the baby back.
سأعيدك أنت والطفل.
Fengyan.
فنغيان.
I hope that our child
أتمنى أن يكون طفلنا
has a complete family
عائلة كاملة
and grows up in the love of the parents.
وينمو في حب الوالدين.
No worries.
لا داعى للقلق.
For now,
الآن،
nothing is more important than you and the baby.
ما من شيء أهم منك ومن الطفل.
Mengmeng.
مينجمينج.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
Finally, I can be a father.
أخيرًا ، يمكنني أن أصبح أبًا.
(Lingrui Group)
(مجموعة Lingrui)
Cici.
سيسي.
Send this agreement
أرسل هذه الاتفاقية
to Ruide by today.
إلى Ruide اليوم.
Sure, Mr. Jiang.
بالتأكيد ، السيد جيانغ.
Mr. Jiang.
السيد جيانغ.
Would it be a bit too hasty?
هل سيكون متسرعا قليلا؟
The bet-on agreement
اتفاقية الرهان
is a strict assessment
هو تقييم صارم
for both company's operation
لتشغيل كلتا الشركتين
and your marriage life.
وحياة زواجك.
After all, there's still room for negotiation.
بعد كل شيء ، لا يزال هناك مجال للتفاوض.
No improvement is made
لم يتم إجراء أي تحسين
in half of a month.
في نصف شهر.
How dare you bring up my family matters?
كيف تجرؤ على طرح أمور عائلتي؟
Listen up.
اسمع.
The priority now
الأولوية الآن
is to get the company to go public.
هو جعل الشركة تصبح عامة.
Mr. Jiang.
السيد جيانغ.
One week.
اسبوع واحد.
Please give us one more week.
يرجى إعطائنا أسبوعًا إضافيًا.
I can use this period to hire someone to replace you instead.
يمكنني استخدام هذه الفترة لتوظيف شخص ليحل محلك بدلاً من ذلك.
Get out.
اخرج.
Ahem.
اهم.
Cici.
سيسي.
Yes.
نعم.
Send Mrs. Chu an invitation
أرسل دعوة للسيدة تشو
of the IPO Annoucement.
إعلان الاكتتاب.
Sure.
بالتأكيد.
I'll do it now.
سأفعل ذلك الآن.
(Bet-on Agreement)
(اتفاقية الرهان)
(Jiang Fengyan)
(جيانغ فنغيان)
Mrs. Chu.
السيدة تشو.
The agreement of Lingrui is here.
اتفاق Lingrui هنا.
Besides,
بجانب،
this is the invitation from them.
هذه هي الدعوة منهم.
Make a move now.
تحرك الآن.
It's time to make good on our promise.
حان الوقت للوفاء بوعدنا.
Don't miss out on the good timing.
لا تفوت الوقت المناسب.
Okay.
تمام.
You spend so much time on that woman.
أنت تقضي الكثير من الوقت على تلك المرأة.
How's it now?
كيف الحال الان؟
(You spy on me.)
(أنت تتجسس علي.)
Hmph.
همف.
You promised me
لقد وعدتني
to settle all these as soon as you can.
لتسوية كل هذه بأسرع ما يمكن.
Why?
لماذا؟
Do you regret it now?
هل تندم على ذلك الآن؟
(I've told you this isn't simple.)
(لقد أخبرتك أن هذا ليس بالأمر السهل.)
Don't expose yourself
لا تعرض نفسك
and leave any flaws behind.
وتترك أي عيوب خلفك.
You should know the consequence.
يجب أن تعرف النتيجة.
(I need some more time.)
(أحتاج المزيد من الوقت.)
Show me
أرِنِي
what you got.
ماذا لديك.
(Lingrui Group)
(مجموعة Lingrui)
Thank you for taking time out of your busy schedule
شكرا لك على قضاء بعض الوقت خارج جدولك المزدحم
(Lingrui Group's IPO Announcement) to attend Lingrui's IPO Announcement.
(إعلان الاكتتاب العام لمجموعة Lingrui) لحضور إعلان الاكتتاب العام لشركة Lingrui.
I'd like to express
أود أن أعبر
my gratitude to my staff,
امتناني لموظفيي ،
board of directors,
مجموعة مخرجين،
investors
المستثمرين
and friends who have been by Lingrui's side all the way.
والأصدقاء الذين كانوا بجانب Lingrui طوال الطريق.
I want to thank one person in particular.
أريد أن أشكر شخصًا واحدًا على وجه الخصوص.
Because she's been accompanying me
لأنها كانت ترافقني
and supporting both Lingrui and me.
ودعم كل من Lingrui وأنا.
This person
هذا الشخص
is my wife.
هي زوجتي.
Her presence
حضورها
has granted Lingrui courage
منح Lingrui الشجاعة
and granted me a sense of stability.
ومنحني شعورا بالاستقرار.
Why?
لماذا؟
Didn't Jiang Fengyan date you in secret?
ألم يواعدك جيانغ فنغيان سرا؟
I'll wire seventy million
سأسلك سبعين مليون
to your account right now.
لحسابك الآن.
Please keep your promise.
يرجى الوفاء بوعدك.
Well done, Xiang Meng.
أحسنت ، شيانغ منغ.
It's the first time
أنها المرة الأولى
that I'm impressed by you.
أني معجب بك.
Thanks to you,
شكرا لك،
Fengyan
فنغيان
gave me a ring yesterday.
أعطاني خاتم أمس.
Are you sure everything you do is worth it?
هل أنت متأكد من أن كل ما تفعله يستحق كل هذا العناء؟
Of course.
بالتاكيد.
I've been waiting this moment
كنت أنتظر هذه اللحظة
for five years.
لمدة خمس سنوات.
Five years?
خمس سنوات؟
Did you break your ligament five years ago
هل كسرت رباطك قبل خمس سنوات
on a purpose?
عن قصد؟
Because you wanted to approach Jiang Fengyan?
لأنك أردت الاقتراب من Jiang Fengyan؟
You just realised this today?
هل أدركت هذا اليوم؟
As expected from the great daughter of Xu Qing.
كما هو متوقع من الابنة العظيمة شو تشينغ.
Using your dance career
استخدام مهنتك في الرقص
and five years of youth
وخمس سنوات من الشباب
for a chance
للحصول على فرصة
to intrude into other's family in return.
للتطفل على عائلة الآخر في المقابل.
Speaking as someone who's been through a lot,
أتحدث كشخص مر بالكثير ،
obtaining the love of Jiang Fengyan
الحصول على حب جيانغ فنغيان
isn't the best choice for you.
ليس الخيار الأفضل لك.
Don't you worry about me.
لا تقلق علي.
You should care about yourself instead.
يجب أن تهتم بنفسك بدلاً من ذلك.
My
لي
dear sister.
أختي العزيزة.
Both of us know very well
كلانا يعرف جيدا
that Jiang Fengyan regards marriage
أن جيانغ فنغيان يعتبر الزواج
as a tool to pursue what he wants.
كأداة لمتابعة ما يريد.
And you've been trapped in the mire.
وأنت محاصر في الوحل.
This is
هذا هو
a present for you.
هدية لك.
A wedding present.
هدية زفاف.
Isn't it something you've coveted?
أليس هذا شيئًا كنت تطمع إليه؟
Mr. Chu.
السيد.  تشو.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
آسف لجعلك تنتظر.
Mrs. Chu has offered you
عرضت عليك السيدة تشو
a lot of benefits.
الكثير من الفوائد.
Why did you know about it?
لماذا علمت عنها؟
It's easy.
من السهل.
And I know
وأنا أعرف
more about you too.
المزيد عنك أيضًا.
What do you want?
ماذا تريد؟
You're merely a pawn in the game.
أنت مجرد بيدق في اللعبة.
If the plan is exposed,
إذا تم الكشف عن الخطة ،
do you think
هل تعتقد
Mrs. Chu would still keep you in check?
السيدة "تشو" هل ستبقيك تحت المراقبة؟
I'm not interested in what she wants to do.
أنا لست مهتمًا بما تريد أن تفعله.
But, don't you lay your finger on Xiang Wei,
لكن ، لا تضع إصبعك على Xiang Wei ،
otherwise, you'll regret for what you do.
وإلا فسوف تندم على ما تفعله.
♪If you insist on leaving, I'll let you go♪
♪ إذا أصررت على المغادرة ، فسأطلق سراحك ♪
♪My love for you, I'll keep it♪
♪ حبي لك ، سأحتفظ به ♪
♪Encountering you in a different world♪
♪ مواجهتك في عالم مختلف ♪
♪I'm content♪
♪ أنا راضٍ ♪
♪With what I possessed before♪
بما كنت أملكه من قبل ♪
♪An unexpected love♪
♪ حب غير متوقع ♪
♪Is an abrupt blessing♪
هي نعمة فجائية
♪Regardless of whether your love is genuine or not♪
♪ بغض النظر عما إذا كان حبك حقيقي أم لا
♪Your place in my heart never changes♪
مكانتك في قلبي لا تتغير
♪Even if I have to be punished for falling for you♪
♪ حتى لو كان يجب أن أعاقب لوقوعك في حبك ♪
♪I'm not afraid of that♪
♪ لست خائفًا من ذلك ♪
♪Bring it on. I won't back down♪
اجلبه.  لن أتراجع ♪